A Guide to the Thomas H. Hunter Collection 1934-1995
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- HUNTER ADDITION
  - JOHN SHERMAN COOPER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1967-1985, TD, TLS, PHOTO, ALS (Box-folder 01-42)
    ANNE INTERESTED IN VIETNAM--CONGRESSIONAL SPEECH, ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN MEDICAL COLLEGES
  - NORMAN COUSINS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1958-1990, TLS (Box-folder 01-43)
    THE PHOENIX DEFENSE FUND
  - EDWARD P. CAWLEY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1960-1980, ALS, TLS (Box-folder 01-44)
    UVA DEPARTMENT OF DERMATOLOGY
  - WILLIAM CRADDOCK 1966, TLS (Box-folder 01-45)
    NEURORADIOLOGY FELLOWSHIP IN NORWAY
  - CATHERINE CRIGLER GERHARDT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1958-1959, ALS, PHOTO (Box-folder 01-46)
  - GAYLE CRUTCHFIELD TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968, ALS (Box-folder 01-47)
    UVA DEPARTMENT OF NEUROLOGICAL SURGERY
  - NICHOLAS DAVIES TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1986, TLS (Box-folder 01-48)
  - BERNARD DAVIS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1963-1992, TD, ALS, TLS, TLS, TM, CARD/PHOTO (Box-folder 01-49)
    HARVARD MEDICAL SCHOOL ADELE LEHMAN PROFESSOR OF BACTERIAL PHYSIOLOGY, NEO-LYSENKIOSM, IQ, AND THE PRESS, CELLS AND SOULS, GOVERNMENT AND QUALITY IN SCIENCE, SCIENCE AND POLITICS
  - ALBERT DAW TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1992, TLS (Box-folder 01-50)
    SOUTHSIDE SURGICAL ASSOCIATES, INC., THOMAS H. HUNTER A GOOD COUNSELOR
  - HENRY DAWSON AND MARJORIE DAWSON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1944-1956, ALS, TLS, CARD, TAX (Box-folder 01-51)
  - H. R. DEAN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1941, TLS (Box-folder 01-52)
    PATHOLOGY DEPARTMENT UNIVERSITY OF CAMBRIDGE
  - DEARING JOHNS, (MRS. HARRY T. LEWIS) TO ANNE HUNTER, THOMAS H. HUNTER 1961-1994, ALS, TLS, TD, CARD, PHOTO, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 01-53)
    UVA DEPARTMENT OF NEUROLOGY
  - JOHN DENSMORE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1994, ALS, TD, TLS (Box-folder 01-54)
    RECOMMENDATION FOR RESIDENCY TRAINING
  - HARDY C. DILLARD TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1966-1980, TD, MEMORABILIA, TLS, TLS (Box-folder 01-55)
    DEAN OF UVA LAW SCHOOL
  - LEIGH DONOWITZ TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1993, ALS/CARD (Box-folder 01-56)
  - WILLIAM H. DRAPER, JR. TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966, TD, TLS (Box-folder 01-57)
    PLANNED PARENTHOOD--WORLD POPULATION
  - RAYMOND S. DUFF TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1979, TLS (Box-folder 01-58)
    YALE UNIVERSITY SCHOOL OF MEDICINE
  - EMILY DUKE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1960, ALS (Box-folder 01-59)
    ALBEMARLE COUNTY HISTORICAL SOCIETY
  - MERLIN K. DU VAL TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1988, TLS (Box-folder 01-60)
    SAMARATIN HEALTH SERVICE, FLEXNER AWARD
  - DOUGLAS EASTWOOD TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963-1990, TLS (Box-folder 02-01)
    UVA DEPARTMENT OF ANESTHESIOLOGY
  - ARTHUR EBBERT, JR. TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1988, ALS, TD, PHOTO (Box-folder 02-02)
    CLASSMATE AT HARVARD, ARTIST
  - SIR JOHN ELLIS AND JOAN ELLIS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1957-1994 (?), CARD, PHOTO, ALS, TLS, TD (Box-folder 02-03)
    LONDON HOSPITAL MEDICAL COLLEGE UNIVERSITY OF LONDON DEAN
  - JACK EMMETT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966, TLS, CARD (Box-folder 02-04)
    THOMAS H. HUNTER ILLNESS
  - THOMAS EVANS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1987-1989, CARD, TD (Box-folder 02-05)
    BLASTOMYCOSES DERMATITIDIS
  - NORMA FARBER AND SIDNEY FARBER 1962-1966, CARD (Box-folder 02-06)
  - SEYMOUR FARBER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1942-1945, ALS, TLS, CARD (Box-folder 02-07)
  - MARY FAULKNER AND JIM FAULKNER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1961-1983, ALS, TLS, CARD (Box-folder 02-08)
  - DAVID FEDSON 1990-1994, TD, ALS, TL (Box-folder 02-09)
    IMMUNIZATION, WHO
  - AL FELLER AND ALEEN FELLER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1952-1962, TLS, ALS, CARD (Box-folder 02-10)
    THOMAS H. HUNTER ILLNESS, UVA SOM ASSISTANT DEAN
  - RONALD FERRY AND VIRGINIA PERRY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER (?)-1981, ALS, TLS, ALS, TD, CARD (Box-folder 02-11)
  - EDWARD FISCHEL TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1957-1970, ALS, TD, CARD (Box-folder 02-12)
  - W. LANCELOT FLEMING TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1938-1990, PHOTO, CARD, TLS, ALS, TD (Box-folder 02-13)
    CAMBRIDGE
  - JOHN FLETCHER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1987-1994, TD, TM, TLS, CARD, TLS (Box-folder 02-14)
    DIRECTOR, CENTER FOR BIOMEDICAL ETHICS
  - JOSEPH FLETCHER 1970-1991 (?), TD, TM, TLS, CARD, AL, PHOTO (Box-folder 02-15)
    ETHICS
  - ETHEL FLOREY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1953-1964, ALS, CARD (Box-folder 02-16)
  - EUGENE FOSTER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1993-1994, TD, TLS (Box-folder 02-17)
    ALTERNATIVE CURRICULUM PROGRAM
  - DONALD FREDERICKSON 3-1990, TD (Box-folder 02-18)
    NIH
  - FRANK FREMONT-SMITH TO ANNE HUNTER 3-1957, TLS (Box-folder 02-19)
  - HARRY FRITTS ?, TD (Box-folder 02-20)
    ON THE NATURE OF THE DIAPHRAGM: THE EVOLUTION OF THREE VIEWPOINTS
  - VICTOR FUCHS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 9-1977, TLS (Box-folder 02-21)
    NATIONAL BUREAU OF ECONOMIC RESEARCH, INC, WHILE AT STANFORD
  - PIERRE GALLETTI TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1984, TLS (Box-folder 02-22)
  - JAMES GAMBLE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1945-1959, TLS, CARD (Box-folder 02-23)
    HARVARD MEDICAL SCHOOL DEPARTMENT OF PEDIATRICS
  - JEAN GARDNER TO ANNE HUNTER, THOMAS H. HUNTER JULY 1963, ALS (Box-folder 02-24)
    JOURNAL OF ENDOCRINOLOGY
  - R. W. GARNETT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER AUGUST 1963, TLS (Box-folder 02-25)
  - JOSEPH GAYLES TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1985-1988, TLS (Box-folder 02-26)
    MOREHOUSE SCHOOL OF MEDICINE
  - WILLARD GAYLIN 1993, TD (Box-folder 02-27)
    FAULTY DIAGNOSIS, WHY CLINTON'S HEALTH-CARE PLAN WONT CURE WHAT AILS US
  - NICHOLAS GEMMA TO THOMAS H. HUNTER MAY 1989, TLS (Box-folder 02-28)
    UVA MEDICAL CHEIF RESIDENT
  - CHALMERS GEMMILL TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1961-1968, CARD, TLS (Box-folder 02-29)
    UVA PROFESSOR OF PHARMACOLOGY
  - MARJORIE ROWLAND GERHARDT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1963, ALS, TLS (Box-folder 02-30)
    WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY SCHOOL OF MEDICINE
  - HUGUETTE GHALIOUNGUI AND PAUL GHALIOUNGUI TO ANNE HUNTER, THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968-?, TLS, CARD (Box-folder 02-31)
    KUWAIT
  - MARY GIBSON AND ROBERT GIBSON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 12-1990, TD, TLS, CARD (Box-folder 02-32)
    UVA DEPARTMENT OF INTERNAL MEDICINE
  - CARL GILBERT AND HELEN GILBERT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1983, ALS, TD (Box-folder 02-33)
  - A. J. GILL TO ANNE HUNTER 1959, TLS (Box-folder 02-34)
    DEAN OF SOUTHWESTERN MEDICAL SCHOOL, UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS
  - HOWARD GILLETTE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1988-1990, CARD, ALS (Box-folder 02-35)
    CLASSMATE OF THOMAS H. HUNTER AT HARVARD
  - ROBERT J. GLASER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947, 1994 (Box-folder 02-36)
    DEAN, UNIVERSITY OF COLORADO SOM, HENRY KAISER FAMILY FOUNDATION, LUCILLE MARKEY CHARITABLE TRUST, THE PHAROS, HARVARD MEDICAL ALUM
  - "COTTON" GLASS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966, CARD (Box-folder 02-37)
  - MILLS GODWIN AND KATHERINE GODWIN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1968 (?), ALS, CARD (Box-folder 02-38)
    GOVERNOR OF VIRGINIA
  - BRAZIL DE GOES TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1964, CARD (Box-folder 02-39)
    UNIVERSITY OF BRAZIL
  - CYNTHIA GOLDSTEIN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1994, TD, CARD (Box-folder 02-40)
    BOOK OF JOB
  - GERRY GOLDSTEIN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966, ALS (Box-folder 02-41)
  - CARLOS GOMEZ 1991-1992, TD (Box-folder 02-42)
    EUTHANASIA
  - JORGE GOMEZ TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1964, TLS (Box-folder 02-43)
    CALI, COLUMBIA
  - LUIS GONZALEZ-MEZABORN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER I-1965, ALS (Box-folder 02-44)
  - FLORINE GOOCH TO ANNE HUNTER 1958-1966, ALS, TD (Box-folder 02-45)
    LIBERAL ARTS SEMINARS UVA
  - ED GOODMAN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 4-1943, ALS (Box-folder 02-46)
    U.S. NAVEL HOSPITAL, PORTSMOUTH, VA
  - NORMAN A. GRAEBNER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1987-1990, TLS, TD (Box-folder 02-47)
    UVA FALL 1987 CONVOCATION--TRADITION, THE FOUNDING FATHERS AND FOREIGN AFFAIRS
  - HELEN GRAHAM TO ANNE HUNTER, THOMAS H. HUNTER 1954- (?), ALS, CARD/PHOTO (Box-folder 02-48)
  - BRADLEY GRAY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 12-1966, ALS (Box-folder 02-49)
  - MARTIN GREENBERGER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 10-1980, TLS (Box-folder 02-50)
    PALO ALTO
  - DAVID GREENE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1943-1994, TLS, ALS, TD, PHOTO, CARD (Box-folder 03-01)
    MEDICAL SCHOOL CLASSMATE OF THOMAS H. HUNTER
  - ROBERT GREENLEAF AND ESTHER GREENLEAF TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1972-1989, TD, ALS, TLS, CARD (Box-folder 03-02)
  - DAVID GREER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 3-1984, TLS (Box-folder 03-03)
    DEAN OF BROWN UNIVERSITY MEDICAL SCHOOL
  - PAUL GRINER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1984-1988, TLS (Box-folder 03-04)
    UNIVERSITY OF ROCHESTER MEDICAL CENTER
  - DIETER GROSCHEL AND MARGARET GROSCHEL TO ANNE HUNTER, THOMAS H. HUNTER 1988-1989, TD, AMS, CARD, ALS (Box-folder 03-05)
  - PAUL GROSS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER OCTOBER 1992, TLS (Box-folder 03-06)
    UVA CENTER FOR ADVANCED STUDIES
  - JOHN LIPPENCOTT GUERRANT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963-1984, TLS, TD, CARD, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 03-07)
    UVA INTERNAL MEDICINE
  - RICHARD GUERRANT 1985-1994, TD, CARD, TLS (Box-folder 03-08)
    UVA INTERNATIONAL MEDICINE
  - DUPONT GUERRY AND SALLY GUERRYTO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1993, TD, MEMORABILIA, CARD (Box-folder 03-09)
  - SAUL GUSBURG TO THOMAS H. HUNTER MAY 1963, TD (Box-folder 03-10)
    THE TEACHING HOSPITAL EXPERIENCE
  - HANS-JURGEN GUTH TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1986, TLS, TD (Box-folder 03-11)
    ARTICLE IN GERMAN--MEDICAL CENTER HOUR
  - ERNESTO GUTIEREZ TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963-64, TLS, CARD (Box-folder 03-12)
    COLUMBIA, IN SPANISH
  - JAVIER GUTIEREZ TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963, TLS, CARD (Box-folder 03-13)
    CALI, COLUMBIA, IN SPANISH
  - ALEXANDER GUTMAN MARCH 1942, TLS (Box-folder 03-14)
    ROCKERFELLER FOUNDATION
  - GARRETT HARDIN 1976-1995, TD, TLS (Box-folder 03-15)
    IMMIGRATION, POPULATION CONTROL
  - ROBERT HARRIS AND DASHIEL HARRIS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER AUGUST 1966, TLS (Box-folder 03-16)
  - ANDREW HART TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1955-1983, ALS, AN, TD, CARD (Box-folder 03-17)
  - MCGEHEE HARVEY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1968-1986, ALS, TLS, TD (Box-folder 03-18)
    ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN PHYSICIANS, JOHNS HOPKINS
  - HALSTEAD HEDGES 1961-1992, TD, ALS (Box-folder 03-19)
    B. 1867--EARLY CHARLOTTESVILLE PHYSICIAN--ENT
  - MICHAEL HEIDELBERGER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1952-1991, CARD, TM (Box-folder 03-20)
  - ROBERT HERRICK TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1941-1942, TLS (Box-folder 03-21)
    HARVARD CREW
  - BRUCE JAY HILLMAN JANUARY 1994, TD (Box-folder 03-22)
    CURRICULUM VITAE
  - EDWARD W. HOOK 1979-1995, TLS, TD, TM (Box-folder 03-23)
    CURRICULUM VITAE, UVA MEDICAL CENTER HOUR, INFECTIOUS DISEASE AND INTERNAL MEDICINE
  - EDWARD W. HOOK TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1988-1993, PHOTO, SLIDE, ALS, TD, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 03-24)
    CHAIRMAN, UVA DEPARTMENT OF MEDICINE
  - GANTT HORSLEY 1962-1980, AN, TD (Box-folder 03-25)
    NATIONAL MEDICINE, ROCKERFELLER FOUNDATION
  - A. E. DICK HOWARD TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1975-1995, TD, TLS, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 03-26)
    UVA SCHOOL OF LAW
  - BEN HUBBY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1989, TLS, TD (Box-folder 03-27)
    UVA SOM GRADUATE, 1965, ESSY ABOUT UVA MEDICAL SCHOOL, DEAN HUNTER, DR. PARSON, WHY WENT TO MED SCHOOL, ETC.
  - DICK HUDGENS AND ALLETTA HUDGINS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER JULY 1963, CARD (Box-folder 03-28)
  - SLUG HUMPHRIES AND ZAIDA HUMPHRIES TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1991, ALS (Box-folder 03-29)
  - LOTTA HUNT AND ANDREW D. HUNT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1981-1984, ALS (Box-folder 03-30)
  - ANDREW HUXLEY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1942-1994, ALS, CARD, PHOTO, TD (Box-folder 03-31)
    FRIEND FROM CAMBRIDGE
  - FRANZ INGELFINGER AND SARAH INGELFINGER 1962-1966, CARD (Box-folder 03-32)
  - JOHN JEFFRIES TO THOMAS H. HUNTER DEC. 1978, ALS (Box-folder 03-33)
  - WILLIAM JEFFRIES TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1989-1993, TLS (Box-folder 03-34)
  - WANSBOROUGH JONES TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1939, ALS (Box-folder 03-35)
    TRINITY HALL, CAMBRIDGE
  - ALBERT JONSE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1982, ALS, TD (Box-folder 03-36)
    CLINICAL ETHICS
  - WILLIAM S. JORDAN, JR. AND MARION JORDAN TO ANNE HUNTER, THOMAS H. HUNTER 1960-?, CARD/PHOTO, TLS, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 03-37)
  - LUIS CARLOS JUNQUERA TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963-1968, ALS, TLS, PHOTO (Box-folder 03-38)
    SAO PAULO, BRAZIL
  - JOSE JURADO AND MARCY JURADO TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1964-1977, TLS, ALS (Box-folder 03-39)
    CALI, COLUMBIA--IN SPANISH
  - ELVIN KABAT 1983, TD (Box-folder 03-40)
  - EDGAR KAFAULA TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1963, ALS (Box-folder 03-41)
    COLUMBIA--IN SPANISH
  - RUTH KAHLER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1956-1964, ALS, $ (Box-folder 03-42)
  - DAN KAHNMAN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER DEC. 1978, CARD/AL (Box-folder 03-43)
  - LEON KASS 1991-92, TD, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 03-44)
    ORGANS FOR SALE
  - THEODORE E. KEATS, CURRICULUM VITAE, TD (Box-folder 04-01)
  - FINCH KELLER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963-1969, APS, TLS, ALS (Box-folder 04-02)
    BELMONT HILL SCHOOL
  - T. A. KEMP AND RUTH KEMP TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1967-1971, APS, CARD, ALS, TLS, TD (Box-folder 04-03)
    ENGLAND
  - WILLIAM KEPNER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1965, ALS, TD (Box-folder 04-04)
  - GORDON KEPPEL AND PEGGY KEPPEL TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1942-1979, ALS, ANS, TD, CARD, PHOTO (Box-folder 04-05)
    AT CAMBRIDGE TOGETHER
  - CLARK KERR TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1965, TLS, TD (Box-folder 04-06)
    UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA AT BERKELY PRESIDENT
  - JOHN KIBUKEMASAKE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1967-1968, ALS, CARD (Box-folder 04-07)
  - JOSEPHINE KIGGUNCHI TO ANNE HUNTER 1968, ALS (Box-folder 04-08)
    UGANDA
  - RICHARD KING AND JILLETT KING TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1983, TLS, ALS (Box-folder 04-09)
  - JOAN ECHTENKAMP KLEIN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1988-1990, ALS, TLS, TD (Box-folder 04-10)
    CURATOR, UVA CLAUDER MOORE HEALTH SCIENCES LIBRARY HISTORICAL COLLECTIONS
  - ALLAN KLINE AND HEANNE KLINE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1949-1993, ALS, TLS, CARD, MEMORABILIA, PHOTO, TD (Box-folder 04-11)
    PHOTO OF THOMAS H. HUNTER AND ANNE HUNTER, 1983
  - GENE KLINGBERG AND JEAN KLINGBERG TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1956-1968, TLS, CS, PHOTO (Box-folder 04-12)
  - MICHAEL KLINGMAN 1993 (?), TD (Box-folder 04-13)
    COMFORT CARE AND PHYSICIAN ASSISTED SUICIDE
  - WALTER KLINGMAN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1978, ALS (Box-folder 04-14)
  - JIM KNOWLES TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1943, ALS (Box-folder 04-15)
  - JOHN H. KNOWLES AND EDITH LACROIX KNOWLES TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1954 (?)-1982, PHOTO/CARD, TD, TLS, ALS, AD, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 04-16)
    BELMONT HILL SCHOOL, HARVARD GRADUATE, MASS GENERAL DIRECTOR, NOMINATED SEC. HEALTH AND SCIENTIFIC AFFAIRS, ROCKERFELLER FOUNDATION PRESIDENT, WROTE ABOUT TOM'S ILLNESS
  - FRANK KNOWLTON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1988-1989, TLS (Box-folder 04-17)
    HARVARD CLASS OF 1935
  - DIETER KOCH-WESER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, FAMILY 1965-1968, ALS, TD, CARD (Box-folder 04-18)
  - ROBERT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963-1970 (?), ALS, TLS, CARD, PHOTO, MAP, TD (Box-folder 04-19)
    IN CALI TOGETHER (?)
  - THADDEUS KOSTRUBALA TO THOMAS H. HUNTER ?-1988, ALS, CARD (Box-folder 04-20)
    UVA MEDICAL STUDENT CLASS FO 1958
  - RUNI KRAUS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976, CARD (Box-folder 04-21)
  - DENNIS KREBS AND JUDY KREBS TO ANNE HUNTER 1977-1979, ALS, TD (Box-folder 04-22)
  - DON KUPKE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1991, TLS (Box-folder 04-23)
    COMMENTS ON PHILOSOPHICAL DISCUSSIONS WITH THOMAS H. HUNTER
  - ZOFIA KURATOWSKA 1962, TLS, ALS (Box-folder 04-24)
    POLAND
  - HARRY B. LAKE AND DULCIE LAKE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1963-1968, CARD (Box-folder 04-25)
  - LINO LIPINSKY 1949-?, PHOTO, ART TD (Box-folder 04-25)
    PHOTOS OF ARTWORK BY LIPINSKY, PAMPHLET FEATURE L.
  - LUANN LANDON TO ANNE HUNTER 1981, TD, CARD (Box-folder 04-26)
    POETRY
  - INA LANGMAN AND JAN LANGMAN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1968-1991, TLS, TD, CARD (Box-folder 04-27)
    UVA CHAIRMAN, DEPARTMENT OF ANATOMY
  - CLARK LAWRENCE AND ELEANOR LAWRENCE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1954-1967, PHOTO/CARD, ANS (Box-folder 04-28)
    CISMONT NEIGHBORS
  - BYRD STUART LEAVELL AND NANCY LEAVELL CORRESPONDENCE WITH THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1962-1980, ALS, TLS, TL, CARD (Box-folder 04-29)
    PERSONAL LETTER FROM THOMAS H. HUNTER DURING ILLNESS, UVA SOM
  - A. G. LEISHMAN AND PEGGYLEISHMAN 1950-1983, ALS (Box-folder 04-30)
    REFERS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER AS "BEVIS"
  - CARLOS LEON AND NAZLE LEON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1963-1994, TLS, CARD, TD (Box-folder 04-31)
    CALI, COLUMBIA, SOME IN SPANISH
  - GRANT LIDDLE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1965-1967, TLS, ALS, CARD (Box-folder 04-32)
    VANDERBUILT UNIVERSITY
  - ROBERT G. LINDEE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER FEB. 1979, TLS (Box-folder 04-33)
    VICE PRESIDENT OF HENRY KAISER FAMILY FOUNDATION
  - ROBERT LINDSAY AND HELEN LINDSAY TO ANNE HUNTER, THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-?, TLS, CARD, ALS, PHOTO (Box-folder 04-34)
  - LINO LIPINSKY AND LEAH LIPINSKY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1957-85, ASL, ART/CARD, TD/ART (Box-folder 04-36)
    DRAWINGS ON LETTERS BY LIPINSKY
  - LINO LIPINSKY AND LEAH LIPINSKY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1950-1994, CARD/CARD, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 04-37)
    ARTWORK ON (MOST) CARDS BY LINO LIPINSKY
  - ANNIE G. LIPSCOMB TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1962-1990, TLS, CARD, ALS, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 04-38)
    ANNIE LIPSCOMB WAS THE LONG-TIME SECRETARY TO UVA'S MEDICAL SCHOOL, LETTERS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER IN CALI AND DURING ILLNESS, COMMENTS ON JFK AND DESEGREGATION
  - JIM LITTLEFIELD TO THOMAS H. HUNTER AUG. 1966, ALS (Box-folder 04-39)
  - ROBERT F. LOEB AND EMILY LOEB TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1961-1973, ALS, CARD/ALS (Box-folder 04-40)
    REGIUS PROFESSOR MEDICINE, UNIVERSITY OF OXFORD
  - IRVING LONDON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER JAN. 1969, TLS (Box-folder 04-41)
    ALBERT EINSTEIN COLLEGE OF MEDICINE
  - HECTOR LONDONO AND SOPHY LONDONO TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1963-1978, ALS, PHOTO, TELEGRAM (Box-folder 04-42)
  - WILLIAM BOYD LOONEY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1992, ALS, TD, TLS (Box-folder 04-43)
    RADIOBIOLOGY
  - RAFAEL LOREDO TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963-1964, TLS, CARD (Box-folder 04-44)
    LIMA, PERU, IN SPANISH
  - OLIVER H. LOWERY, NORMA LOWERY, AND ADRIENNE LOWERY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1953-1994, PHOTO, CARD, ALS, TD, TLS (Box-folder 05-01)
    WASHINGTON UNVERSITY SOM
  - OLIVER H. LOWERY AND ADRIENNE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1964-1995, CARD, ALS, PHOTO, TD (Box-folder 05-02)
    ARTWORK BY A. LOWERY, WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY SOM
  - THEODORE LOWI 1967, TD (Box-folder 05-03)
    MAKING DEMOCRACY WORK, PUBLIC PHILOSOPHY
  - MARTY LOWRANCE AND PRES LOWRANCE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1963-1977, ALS, CARD (Box-folder 05-04)
  - PATRICIA M. LOZANO TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1964, ALS (Box-folder 05-05)
    SOME IN SPANISH
  - HUGH MACMILLAN AND LINDSAY MACMILLAN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1943-1992, ALS, CARD, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 05-06)
  - GERALD L. MANDELL TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1991-1994, TD, AM (Box-folder 05-07)
    INFECTIOUS DISEASE
  - SAM R. MARNEY, JR. AND BETTY MARNEY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1963-1991, CARD, ALS (Box-folder 05-08)
    STUDENT OF THOMAS H. HUNTER
  - ANNE HUNTER TO MARY FAITH MARSHALL 1991-1992, TD, TL (Box-folder 05-09)
    WORKING WITH JOSEPH FLETCHER
  - VICTOR MARSHALL TO ANNE HUNTER 1991, ALS (Box-folder 05-10)
  - MARTHA A. MARTIN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER JAN-APRIL 1992, TD, TLS, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 05-11)
    FRIENDS OF THE CENTER FOR BIOMEDICAL ETHICS
  - JOHN A. MARTIN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER MAY 1989, ALS (Box-folder 05-12)
    UVA MED GRAD 1989
  - JOSEPH A. MCDONALD, JR. AND JO JANETTE MCDONALD TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1952-1966, TLS, CARD/PHOTO (Box-folder 05-13)
  - BOB MCGILVERY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1961, TLS (Box-folder 05-14)
  - LOCKHART MCGUIRE AND ANNE BEMIS 1967-1994, ALS, TD, TLS, CARD, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 05-15)
    ARTICLE AND PERSONAL COMMENTS ON HEALTH AND MEDICAL ETHICS, DETAILED REPORT ON THOMAS H. HUNTER HEALTH (1987)
  - RUSTIN MCINTOSH AND MILLICENT MCINTOSH TO ANNE HUNTER, THOMAS H. HUNTER 1954-1986, AMS, CARD, TLS (Box-folder 05-16)
  - COLIN MCLEOD TO ANNE HUNTER JAN 1969, ALS (Box-folder 05-17)
  - MARGARET MEAD TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 9-20-1968, TLS (Box-folder 05-18)
    STEERING COMMITTE, INSTITUTE ON MEDICAL EDUCATION AND FAMILY PLANNING
  - CLIFTON K. MEADOR TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1994, TD, ALS, TLS (Box-folder 05-19)
    DEAN, UNIVERSITY OF ALABAMA SCHOOL OF MEDICINE
  - PETER MEDAWAR, PETER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1982, ALS, TD, CARD (Box-folder 05-20)
    1960 NOBEL PRIZE WINNER, BRITISH
  - DIEGO MEJIA AND MARIA MIEJO TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1963-1992, ALS, CARD, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 05-21)
  - RAPHAEL MELGAR TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1964-1979, ALS, CARD/PHOTO (Box-folder 05-22)
  - THOMAS C. MENDENHALL TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1986, ALS, CARD (Box-folder 05-23)
    THOMAS H. HUNTER IN HIS BROTHER'S MEDICAL SCHOOL CLASS
  - HERMAN MENDOSA NOV. 1960-61, TD (Box-folder 05-24)
    COLUMBIA, VISITED UVA
  - WALTER MENNINGER AND CONNIE MENNINGER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1976-1984, TD, CARD (Box-folder 05-25)
  - STEPHANIE METCALF TO THOMAS H. HUNTER DEC 1963, ALS (Box-folder 05-26)
  - MARJORIE MIALE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1977-1980, PHOTO, CARD (Box-folder 05-27)
  - LEIGH B MIDDLEDITCH, JR. TO THOMAS H. HUNTER AUG-NOV 1990, TLS (Box-folder 05-28)
    INTERNATIONAL HEALTH LAW
  - JAMES GRIER MILLER AND JESSIE MILLER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1964-1980, TD, CARD (Box-folder 05-29)
    PRESIDENT, UNIVERSITY OF LOUISVILLE
  - MARIA MILLER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER APRIL-MAY 1988, ANS, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 05-30)
  - GEORGE MINOR TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967-1992, TM, TD, CARD, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 05-31)
  - J. W. MITCHELL AND VIRGINIA MITCHELL TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1989-1993, TD, CARD (Box-folder 05-32)
  - MARILYN MONROE 1953, GLASS PLATE NEGATIVE (Box-folder 05-33-vault)
    FIRST PLAYBOY CENTERFOLD
  - ROBERT C. MOELLERING, JR. MARCH 1992, TD (Box-folder 05-34)
  - DANIEL NATHAN MOHLER AND HARRIET MOHLER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963-1985, ALS, CARD, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 05-35)
  - MOLECULAR GERIATRICS CORPORATION AUGUST 1993, TM, AN, TD (Box-folder 05-36)
    MOLECULAR GERIATRICS CORPORATION REPRESENTATIVE, FERID MURAND
  - CIRO MERTON MOLINA AND LIZ WINEGAR TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1975-1977(?), TLS,ALS, PHOTO, CARD, TD (Box-folder 05-37)
  - WILHELM MOLL TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963-1966(?), TLS, CARD (Box-folder 06-01)
    UVA MEDICAL LIBRARIAN
  - JOSEPH MOONEYAND BETTY BOWENSEIGNEUR, BETTY 1980, TD (Box-folder 06-02)
  - ROBERT A. MOORE AND RUTH MOORE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1968(?), CARD (Box-folder 06-03)
  - CARL MOORE AND DOROTHY MOORE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963-1972, TLS, CARD (Box-folder 06-04)
    WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY SOM
  - FRANCIS MOORE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977-1984, TLS (Box-folder 06-05)
  - MERRILL MOORE 1955, TD (Box-folder 06-06)
    POEM
  - LORD MORAN APRIL 1967, TD, ALS (Box-folder 06-07)
    CHURCHILL'S PRIVATE PHYSICIAN
  - OTTO MOROWETZ TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963-1993, TLS, ALS, CARD (Box-folder 06-08)
    FORMER PATIENT
  - HAAVI MORREIM TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1982-1992, TLS, TD, ALS (Box-folder 06-09)
    UNIVERSITY OF TENNESSEE SOM
  - HAAVI MORREIM TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1982-1994, PHOTO, CARD (Box-folder 06-10)
  - ROBERT MORISON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1961-1969, TLS, TD, AD (Box-folder 06-11)
    DIRECTOR, ROCKERFELLER FOUNDATION
  - FREDRICK MOSHER MAY 1990, TD (Box-folder 06-12)
    UVA PROFESSOR, OBIT
  - NINO MOWINKLE AND KATE MOWINKLE TO ANNE HUNTER, THOMAS H. HUNTER 1940-1978, TLS, CARD, ALS, TD, PHOTO (Box-folder 06-13)
  - BERT MUDGE AND ELEANOR MUDGE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1962-1967, ALS, CARD (Box-folder 06-14)
  - HENRY MULHOLLAND TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, ANNE HUNTER 1960-1968, ALS, TLS, CARD (Box-folder 06-15)
  - ROBERT M. MUSSELMAN TO ANNE HUNTER 1962-1992, TLS, TD, AN, TELEGRAM (Box-folder 06-16)
    CERTIFIED PUBLIC ACCOUNTANT TO THE HUNTERS
  - WILLIAM H. MULLER, JR. TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963-1989, TLS, TD, MEMORABILIA (Box-folder 06-17)
    UVA DEPARTMENT OF SURGERY
  - GARY C. MURRY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1989, TLS, ALS (Box-folder 06-18)